[Music]
what do churches need guns for I've seen
preachers knocking people over just the
power of the Holy Ghost take it take
it take it take it take it take
it take it take it take it you got Santa
on the no fly list because of see
something say something hey man he's a
bearded dude who comes into this country
dropping off mysterious packages
everywhere these days that's kind of a
problem British scientists use forensics
to uh stitch together uh what they think
Jesus looked like and he's just a little
different than the Jesus most people um
are used to saying you know all these
Christian people and your Mike huckabees
and all these guys are always talking
about Jesus Jesus Jesus this is the kind
of Jesus they wouldn't let into America
which to me makes me makes it really
challenging you know what I mean so
that's for real hey America Larry
Wilmore here if you like the nightly
show on Comedy Central like us on
Facebook too just don't poke me I do not
like being poked you can Candy Crush me